Guide to the Morse College, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Morse College, Yale University, student records
1959-2012
RU 158
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
114.5
(168 boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Morse College, Yale University.
Morse College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-I-1 (YRG 13-I-1), Records of the dean of Morse College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Morse College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Morse College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1963, 1959-1963; Accession 19ND-A-335
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1965, 1961-1965; Accession 19ND-A-336
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1966, 1962-1966; Accession 1971-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1967, 1963-1967; Accession 19ND-A-337
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1964, 1960-1964; Accession 1969-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1968, 1964-1968; Accession 19ND-A-338
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1969, 1965-1969; Accession 19ND-A-339
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1970, 1966-1970; Accession 19ND-A-340
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
  - Ex-Students
- Student records, students withdrawn from the Classes of 1971-1974, 1967-1974; Accession 1983-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050
  - Ex-students 1971
  - Ex-students 1972
  - Ex-students 1973
  - Ex-students 1974
- Student records for the Class of 1971, 1967-1971; Accession 19ND-A-341
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2047
- Student records for the Classes of 1972-1973, 1968-1973; Accession 1978-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2049
  - Class of 1972
  - Class of 1973
- Student records for the Class of 1974, 1970-1974; Accession 1979-A-044
- Student records (impounded) for the Classes of 1975-1978, 1970-1978; Accession 1975-A-014; 5; (6 boxes)
  Restricted until January 1, 2054
- Student records for the Class of 1975, 1971-1975; Accession 1980-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
  Related Materials
  Recommendations for students in the class of 1975 are in RU 158, Accession 19ND-A-342.
  Withdrawn student records for the class of 1975 are in RU 158, Accession 1992-A-006.
- Student records (recommendations) for the Class of 1975, 1971-1975; Accession 19ND-A-342
  Additional student files for the class of 1975 are in RU 158, Accession 1980-A-020.
- Student records for the Class of 1976, 1972-1976; Accession 1981-A-038
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  Letters of recommendation for the class of 1976 are in RU 158 Accession 1983-A-059.
  Withdrawn student records for the class of 1976 are in RU 158, Accession 1992-A-006.
- Student records for the withdrawn students from the Classes of 1975-1977, 1971-1977; Accession 1992-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  Arranged by class, thereunder alphabetically by last name.
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
- Student records for the Class of 1977, 1973-1977; Accession 1982-A-034
  Withdrawn student records for the class of 1977 are in RU 158, Accession 1992-A-006.
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1978, 1974-1978; Accession 1983-A-060
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1979, 1975-1979; Accession 1984-A-038
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 1980, 1976-1980; Accession 1985-A-018
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1981, 1977-1981; Accession 1988-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1982, 1978-1982; Accession 1989-A-036
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1983, 1979-1983; Accession 1990-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1984, 1980-1984; Accession 1992-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1985, 1981-1985; Accession 1993-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1986, 1982-1986; Accession 1994-A-016
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Ex-Students, 1982-1986
- Student records for the Class of 1987, 1983-1987; Accession 1994-A-136
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1988, 1984-1988; Accession 1995-A-075
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1989, 1985-1989; Accession 1996-A-068
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1990, 1986-1990; Accession 2001-A-101
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1991, 1987-1991; Accession 2002-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1992, 1988-1992; Accession 2003-A-064
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1993, 1989-1993; Accession 2004-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1994, 1990-1994; Accession 2004-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 2005-A-074
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1996, 1992-1996; Accession 2006-A-160
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - WITHDREW
- Student records for the Class of 1997, 1993-1997; Accession 2007-A-067
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1998, 1994-1998; Accession 2008-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1999, 1995-1999; Accession 2009-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 2000, 1995-2000; Accession 2009-A-043
  Restricted unitl Jan 1, 2076.
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 2001, 1997-2001; Accession 2009-A-167
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 2002, 1998-2002; Accession 2009-A-170
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 2003, 1999-2003; Accession 2011-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2079
  - WITHDRAWN
- Student records for the Class of 2004, 1991-2004; Accession 2011-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2005, 1974-2005; Accession 2012-A-071
  - Withdrawn Students
- Student records for the Class of 2006, 2000-2006; Accession 2014-A-002
  Restricted until January 1, 2081
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2007, 2003-2007; Accession 2015-A-005
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2008, 2005-2008; Accession 2015-A-065
  Restricted until January 1, 2082.
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2009, 2005-2009; Accession 2017-A-006
  Restricted until January 1, 2085
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 2010, 2006-2010; Accession 2018-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2086
- Student records for the Classes of 2011 and 2012, 2007-2012; Accession 2019-A-0010
  Restricted until January 1, 2088
  - Student records, Class of 2011
    - Class folder, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alphonso, Aimee Leigh, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Andrada, Ashley Marie, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Auchincloss, Emily Winthrop, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Ayala, Angel Alexis, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bailey, William Hyatt Hasegawa, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Banks Dobson, Moira Fenno, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Baranay, Melissa Ann, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Barlow, Whithey Ayn, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Blair, Nathaniel Brian, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bolhack, Jessica Lynn, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Buesing, Juliet Kristen, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Carlos, Johathan Edward, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Casey, Robert Donald, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cecil, Jacob Z., 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Cheek, Taja Rae, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chen, George Zhiyu, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Clark, Amanda June, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Coleman, James Gavron, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Collier, Maia Josephine, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Cook, Alexandra C., 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Creager, Anna Sophie, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - DeLeon-Mares, Isaiah Alexander, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - De Silva, Shayari Hiranya, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Dethy, Florence Rose, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Deutsch, Elizabeth Burnat, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Diakun, Anna Natalia, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dill, Brendan, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Dizard, Benjamin Robert, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Eden, Max Campbell, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Evans, Frederick Marshall, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Farrell, Shaun Michael, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Feldman, Andrew Seth, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Feng, Yuzhe (Aiden), 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Fields, Alexandra Margaret, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Gangopadhyay, Deb Sekhar, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Garza, Esteban Ner, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Gerken, Matthew James, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Glienke, Michelle Marie, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Gordon, Victoria Antoinette, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Grunditz, Naomi Rose, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Hakanson, Andrew Francis, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Han, Min-Jung, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Haskins, Amanda Joan, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Hoang Trong, Vi Minh, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Hoffnagle, Elena Easton, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Jeong, Jane, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Katkhuda, Hind Izzeddin, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Kieschnick, Hannah Meredith, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Kroon, Matthew Gerrit, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Kuang, Shan, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Lerman-Tan, Yinshi, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Lieblich, Jerrold Alexander, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Lim, Tse Yang, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Linfield, Rebecca Yaffa, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Lu, Monica Ann, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Lucio, Clara Alejandra, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Macheras, Gustave Ligon, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Mallin, Elisabeth Shamar, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Martin, William, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Marton, Stephanie Ellen, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - McCarthy, Thomas Connor, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - McLoughlin, Samuel Tully, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Megee, Andrew Laurance, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Mitchell, Ezra Parker, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Moedano, Leticia, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Molinas, Alfredo, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Morgan, Taylor Christine, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Mulligan, Stephen Andrew, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Murphy, James Thomas, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Nash, Caroline Sophia, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Nelson, Brynna Ann, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Nguyen, Van Trinh Quoc, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Olusola, Kevin Oluwole, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Pannell, Courtney Brooke, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Pappas, Andrew Michael, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Pareja, David Enrique, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Pyo, Sei Young, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Quintana, Maclovia, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Reisbig, Tara Nicole, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Robinson, Scott Michael, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Robles, William George, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Rondeau, Ryan Chad, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Rotholz, Zachary Paddor, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Rudis, Lilija Antonia, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Samsel, Michael Steven, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Savath, Valentina Lim, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Scrudato, John, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Serventi-Gleeson, Molly, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Silk, Daniel F., 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Sithe, Sibongile Isake, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Smith, David Charles, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Smith, Grant Craig, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Sokoloff, Zachary David, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Starr, Raphael Saul Benjamin, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Stoddard, Thayne Darrell, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Su, Zhuo (Tony), 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Sullivan, Jason Christopher, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Sun, Jinjin, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Tam, Derek Saiho, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Tiwari, Apoorva, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Tokmouline, Mansur Iskanderovitch, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Toth, John William, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Tremonti, Kristina Marie, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Ukah, Adanna Lewe, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Veatch, Kyle Erckson, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Verde, Raffaele, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Waldenberger, Hannah Jane, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Wantchekon, Kristia Armelle, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Warren, Jefferson Cannon, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Warren, Simon Barth, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - West, Abigail Marianne, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Williams, Andrew Mitchell, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Wood, John David Thayer, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Zeugin, Gabriella Martine, 2007-2011 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Student records, Class of 2012
    - Adkisson, Kevin, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Alexander, Andre, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Arrieta, Deanna Marie, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Avner, Janna Rose, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Balvaneda, Bryan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Barcia Duran, Jose-Gabriel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Bautista, Javier Enrique, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Beck, Peter, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Benavides, Marissa, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Benfey, Thomas, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Berry, James, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bhattacharyya, Amarto, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Biondo, Gabriella, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Boone, Matthew, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Caballero, Sandra, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Carlson, Ethan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Chaffetz, Simon, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Chambers, Ana, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Chandran Ashok, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Chang, Caroline, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Chigurupati, Shabdha, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chou, Naomi, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Cohn, Libbie, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Colberg, Lukas, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Cousins, Stephanie, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Diamond, Thaddeus, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Doan, Binh, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Dobies, Justin, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Dyen, Nicholas, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Edwards, Ashley, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Egozi, Sara, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Eichner, Kyle, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Esposito, Andrew, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Farris, Bryan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Fermin, Diandra, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Gass, Joan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Getachew, Bezawit Asheber, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Giacoman, Lissy, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Goodkind, Molly, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Grabar Sage, Henry, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Greenberg, Rafael, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Hadley, Allison, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Hatten, Jeffrey, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Hearn Feldman, Timmia, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Heller, Sloane, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Heroy, John, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Hirsch, Alexander, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Hudak, Justin, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Jones, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Katz, Brian, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Kelly, Madeline, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Kim, Eliot, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Kim, Sunhee Serenity, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Kirkland, Jesse, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Kolata, Justine, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Lau, Tyler, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Lee, Samuel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Meng, Liu (Mary), 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Liuzzi, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Lucido, Andrea, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Lynch, Samuel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Mbaye, Marieme, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - McWilliams, Albert, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Miller, Katherine, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Mittl, Gregory, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Monti, Alexa, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Motala, Tasnim, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Musayev, Olga, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Newell, Kaitlyn, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - O'Duffy, Daniel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - O'Keefe, Rachel, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Patrick, Andrew, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Patrascu, Raul, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Peake, Ian James, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Peng, Elizabeth, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Pyuhn, John, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Reilly, Terrence, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Richards, Lauren, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Rogers, Jordan, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Rosenthal, Adrienne, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Rusciano, Kyle, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Sackler, Rebecca, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Sawaoka, Takuya, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Saxton, Kathryn, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Schulson, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Shah, Monish, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Shoji, Monica, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Socik, Ava, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Stoller, Jacob, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Sun, Tonia, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Szigety, Katherine, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Te, Carol, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Thun-Hohenstein, Sarah, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Tidmarsh, David, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Touchard Pelluz, Pablo, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Tsoi, Gennifer, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Underwood, Leah, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Wade, Edward Matthew, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Waldrop, Virginia, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Walstrom, Sally, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Watty, Stephen, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Willhite, Reginald, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Wynter, Jamila, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Xue, Lisuo (Clark), 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Yap, Ee-Lynn, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Yu, Sherwin, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Zeng, Miao Paul, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Zhong, Lingyuxiu, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Zhou, Xiao-Qiao (Sherry), 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Zhu, Julie, 2008-2012 (Box 2, Folder 110)